let's do another one quiz on btb and BHT
interactions again we have the same BHD
16 entries in perfect btb is four
entries in perfect same program as
before the question for you now is how
many times do we access the btb this
time for each instruction so how many
times when we fetch this instruction do
we access the btb how many times when we
fetch this instruction do we access the
btb and so on remember that these two
instructions execute only once
this Loop has 100 iterations so all
these instructions execute 100 times
except for this one which executes 10
one times the question for you now is
how many times do we access the btb for
each of those instructions